[Music]
[音乐]
all right big crowd thanks for joining
好吧，一大群人感谢您的加入
me because there's also a Josh long talk
我，因为还有一段乔希长话
going on right so just in case you
继续进行下去，以防万一您
missed it you know we can still go there
错过了，你知道我们仍然可以去那里
but thanks for coming to my talk I hope
但是谢谢你来我的演讲
you had a great lunch I really like the
你吃了一顿很棒的午餐，我真的很喜欢
shrimp pasta it was pretty special but
虾意大利面很特别但是
I'm not going to talk about that
我不会谈论这个
obviously I'm going to talk about
显然我将要谈论
cutting edge continuous delivery
尖端的持续交付
automated canary analysis through
通过自动金丝雀分析
spinnaker now that's quite a mouthful
现在的大三角帆
right let me first introduce myself I am
好的，让我先自我介绍我
Andrea severs I'm a solution architect
Andrea服务我是一名解决方案架构师
at pivotal and I am active in the
在关键，我很活跃
application transformation or app TX
应用程序转换或应用程序TX
units within pivotal for amia I used to
我曾经在amia的关键部门内
work for J box and there's a couple of
为J box工作，有几个
ex colleagues here which is pretty cool
前同事在这里，这很酷
and you can reach me on Twitter of
您可以在Twitter上与我联系
course with my true the handle and
当然与我真正的手柄和
receivers also after the talk if you
谈话后的接收者，如果你
have any questions that you didn't get
有没有收到的任何问题
to get an answer on you can always just
得到答案就可以总是
contact me there right so when we talk
在那里联系我，所以当我们说话时
about continuous delivery the ultimate
关于持续交付最终
goal that we try to achieve is to deploy
我们试图实现的目标是部署
software quickly and automatically right
快速自动地正确安装软件
and this can only be achieved if we are
这只有在我们
able to push new code without fear right
无需担心就可以推送新代码
and that's something which I've seen
这是我所见过的
throughout the years even before I
这些年来，甚至在我之前
started doing software developments
开始进行软件开发
there is this kind of these two opposing
这两种对立
forces that try to battle it out on the
试图在
one hand you've got speed and on the
一方面您拥有速度，另一方面
other hand you've got confidence and
另一方面，你有信心
they don't always work together well
他们并不总是能很好地合作
maybe like back in the base when we
也许当我们回到基地时
first started software development at
首先在
least I started for software development
至少我开始从事软件开发
some people used to just change things
有些人过去只是改变事情
in production without testing and you
在生产中无需测试，您
know just hot-swap code perhaps you know
只知道热交换代码，也许你知道
that's gives you a lot of speed but it
那给了你很多速度，但是
doesn't give you any confidence right so
没给你任何信心，所以
then we started adding manual tests but
然后我们开始添加手动测试
manual tests were expensive so we
手动测试很昂贵，所以我们
started grouping features and that led
开始分组功能，导致
to corporate release cycles and those
公司发布周期以及那些
things had a huge impact on speed again
事情再次对速度产生了巨大影响
so while we had increased our confidence
所以虽然我们增加了信心
we had like some speed so then we
我们有一些速度，所以我们
started automating these tests right
开始自动执行这些测试
and that gave us some kind of an extra
这给了我们一些额外的好处
boost in speed but that wasn't enough
加快速度，但这还不够
what we saw throughout these recent
我们在最近的这些经历中看到了什么
years is that we move towards
年是我们走向
architectural modularity for instance
例如建筑模块化
microservices that we could go to
我们可以去的微服务
production faster right these these
这些这些生产速度更快
macro sources are independently
宏源是独立的
deployable units that can go to
可部署的单位
production without having to have this
生产而不必拥有这个
you to recycle but so that gives us an
您可以回收，但是这给了我们一个
extra speed right because you can work
可以提高速度，因为您可以工作
in parallel you can have multiple
平行地你可以有多个
different teams working on multiple
不同的团队从事多个
different services but that doesn't
不同的服务，但这不是
really work for our confidence pretty
真正为我们的信心而努力
well right because now we can't really
好吧，因为现在我们不能真正
have an acceptance environment with all
拥有所有人的接受环境
our microscopes you could do that right
我们的显微镜，你可以做对的
it's possible but that gives you this
有可能，但这给你这个
this coupling again so you have to go
再次耦合，所以你必须去
altogether to production like just if
完全像
you have an environment spun up on
你有一个旋转的环境
acceptance just to test everything in
接受只是为了测试一切
with the certain versions that are
与某些版本
currently in production the moment
目前正在生产中
you've run your tests
您已经进行了测试
production probably has changed already
生产可能已经改变了
right because that's the nature of micro
对，因为这就是微观的本质
services so we had to look at other
服务，所以我们不得不看看其他
alternatives and for one is one option
另一种选择是一种选择
is consuming during contract tests I
在合同测试中消耗了我
don't know anyone heard about that right
不知道有人听说过这项权利
so there's spring tech contract it does
所以有春季技术合同
talk about that tomorrow I think any
我想明天再谈
morning so let's really add a lot of
早上，所以我们真的要添加很多
value it allows you to test your
值，它可以让您测试您的
interactions independently without
独立互动，无
having this huge environment where
拥有如此巨大的环境
everything is deployed on together but
一切都一起部署
it doesn't really test behavior it only
它并没有真正测试行为
tests whether your syntax is correct
测试您的语法是否正确
whether you're contractually sending the
是否按合同发送
right thing I receiving the right thing
我收到正确的东西
right so it doesn't really test whether
对，所以它并没有真正测试是否
the behavior of your service is working
您的服务行为正常
well together with all the other
与其他人一起
services and rather the data in your
服务，而不是您中的数据
databases is actually working well with
数据库实际上与
each other right so that gives us still
彼此正确，所以让我们仍然
a problem for our confidence so you see
我们有信心的一个问题，让您看到
this with micro services you have a lot
借助微服务，您将拥有很多
of speed but you still don't have a lot
的速度，但你仍然没有很多
of confidence or at least you have
有信心或至少你有
limited confidence and then we got a
信心有限，然后我们得到了
look at alternatives right and one of
看看正确的替代方法，其中之一
these alternatives we're gonna be
这些替代方案，我们将成为
talking about today which is called
谈论今天被称为
automated canary analysis so that's I
自动金丝雀分析，所以我
will talk about that a lot but know that
会谈论很多，但是知道
this is kind of something that has been
这有点像
talked about a lot in the past or at
谈论过去或在很多地方
least canary releasing has been talked
讨论过最少的金丝雀释放
about but I've not really found an easy
关于，但我还没有真正找到一个简单的方法
way
方式
to apply it without having a PhD in
在没有博士学位的情况下应用它
mathematics or something right so that's
数学或正确的东西，所以
kind of what spinnaker will we'll bring
我们会带来什么样的大三角帆
to the table so let me first introduce
到桌子上，所以我先介绍一下
spinnaker right spinnaker is a multi
大三角帆右大三角帆是多
clouds
乌云
multi-region deployment tool originally
最初是多区域部署工具
built by Netflix and it supports a lot
由Netflix建立，并且支持很多
of different clouds right a lot of
不同的云对很多
different abstractions one of which is
不同的抽象，其中之一是
cuban at ease so like even any any cloud
轻松自在地孵化，就像任何云一样
that hosts Kubrat is for you will also
主办Kubrat的人也将为您服务
work with spinnaker Cloud Foundry as
与大三角帆Cloud Foundry合作
well to all the different distributions
适用于所有不同的发行版
including pivotal Cloud Foundry and of
包括关键的Cloud Foundry和
course also is so also the major cloud
当然也是主要的云
providers like Azure Amazon Web Services
提供者，如Azure Amazon Web Services
even bare-metal
甚至是裸机
OpenStack this you as a support as well
OpenStack也为您提供支持
if you are using Oracle Oracle cloud and
如果您使用的是Oracle Oracle cloud和
on Google since Google has heavily
在Google上，因为Google
invested in this project they also
他们也投资了这个项目
support App Engine and of course compute
支持App Engine，当然还有计算
engine alright so there's a lot of
好的，所以有很多
clouds that are actually plugging in
实际插入的云
into spinnaker all right so that's
进入大三角帆好吧，那是
that's pretty interesting
那很有趣
so you might wonder like what am i why
所以你可能想知道我为什么
am I talking about spinnaker here yeah
我是在说三角帆吗
on spring i/o right because this is a
在 Spring 我对，因为这是一个
spring conference while the spring team
春季会议，而 The Spring Team
and specifically spring cloud already
特别是 Spring 的云
had something for continuous delivery
有东西要连续交付
they have this thing called spring cloud
他们有这个东西叫做Spring Cloud
pipelines which has been recently
最近的管道
rebranded to cloud pipelines because
更名为云管道，因为
actually that project has nothing to do
实际上那个项目无关
with spring it's just a way to have
Spring 是拥有的一种方式
continuous delivery set up in an easy
轻松设置连续交付
way a paved road where you can have some
一条铺好的路，在那里你可以有一些
kind of a pipeline out of the box with
类似于开箱即用的管道
in the broth steps either in Jenkins or
在詹金斯（Jenkins）或
in concourse so that's already there you
在大厅里，所以已经在那里
can already use that it's been remanded
已经可以使用它已经被还押
to plug the cloud by plants and it has
用植物来塞住云，它有
been kind of given to the community but
被给予社区
I actually do we now refocus with spring
我实际上是在做 Spring 吗
cloud do we refocus to spinnaker while
我们是否将云重新集中到大三角帆上
the reason is here state now where do
原因是这里说明现在在哪里做
you store the state of your cloud while
您在存储云状态的同时
you're actually doing your continuous of
你实际上在做你的连续
delivery where do you get your
交货你从哪里得到
information about what's currently out
有关当前内容的信息
there well cloud pipelines used to use
那里曾经有很好的云管道
or actually uses tags on
或实际上在
right so and yet you can tag if
正确，但是您可以标记是否
something's deployed in a certain
在某些地方部署了某些东西
environment you can tag that commit
您可以标记提交的环境
right so that's that's pretty
对，那就是那漂亮
straightforward
直截了当
however it's also limited right so what
但是它也是有限的，所以
if you do manual deployments and you
如果您进行手动部署，而您
don't go to the pipeline then your whole
不要去管道，然后整个
tagging system is kind of you don't have
标签系统是您所没有的
a lot of confidence in it anymore
对此充满信心
because it might not resemble what's
因为它可能不像什么
currently a production also if you have
目前也有制作
different live versions across different
跨不同的实时版本
regions across different accounts and
不同帐户的区域，以及
different clouds then that's pretty hard
不同的云那么很难
to keep track in just any get repository
跟踪所有get存储库
and if you want to do sophisticated
如果你想做精致的
rollbacks if there's for instance
回滚，如果有的话
multiple versions on production at the
生产中的多个版本
same time and you want to roll back to a
同时，您想回滚到
specific one now that's yeah that's
现在是一个特定的
really difficult with just stagnant so
停滞真的很难
Jenkins and conkers we're sprinkler pipe
詹金斯和七叶树，我们是洒水管
eyes or clad pipelines relies on don't
眼睛或复合管道依赖于
offer the idea of an inventory of some
提供一些库存的想法
kind of repository that keeps track of
一种可以跟踪的存储库
what's currently where your application
您的应用程序目前在哪里
is currently living and that's different
目前正在生活，这是不同的
with spinnaker so a spinnaker gives you
大三角帆，所以大三角帆给你
the inventory across all your different
您所有不同的广告资源
regions all your different clouds and
区域所有您不同的云和
all your different accounts and it
您所有不同的帐户及其
combines that knowledge with pipelines
将知识与管道相结合
that can do really sophisticated stuff
可以做真正复杂的事情
much more sophisticated than your
比你复杂得多
Jenkins or your concourse could ever do
詹金斯或您的大厅可以做到
and we're going to see a demo today
今天我们要看一个演示
about what what that could be all right
关于什么可能没事
so let's first look at look a little bit
所以我们先来看一下
under the hood right so spinnaker under
在引擎盖下，所以大三角帆下
the hood looks surprisingly familiar
引擎盖看起来异常熟悉
right it's just a Microsoft's
对，这只是微软的
architecture if you can call it that at
体系结构，如果可以在
least off spring boot applications right
最少可以使用Spring Boot应用程序
so if you're ever having to troubleshoot
因此，如果您不得不进行故障排除
anything it's gonna be super easy for
任何会变得超级容易的事情
you because this this is just your your
你，因为这只是你的
your regular spring boon applications
您定期的春季优惠申请
there's one in particular which is
特别是有一个是
interesting is halyard it's like a bill
有趣的是挂绳，就像一张账单
of materials for these different macro
这些不同宏的材料
services so different Microsoft's have
微软提供的服务如此不同
different versions and you they kind of
不同的版本，你他们有点
work together with certain certain
与某些人一起工作
versions work which sort of certain
版本可以正常工作
other versions right and Hollyer to make
其他版本的权利和Hollyer可以制作
sure that everything is set correctly a
确保一切设置正确
little bit like your bump in in spring
有点像 Spring 的颠簸
cloud dependencies or spring booty
云依赖或春季战利品
fancies right so it kind of does that as
幻想是正确的，所以这样做
well as a service it also helps you spin
一项服务还可以帮助您旋转
everything up
一切都好
so that's that's kind of how it looks
这就是它的外观
like I know David it also has an angular
就像我知道戴维（David）一样，
UI by the way but enough about that
顺便说一句，但足够的UI
although I have to say since Netflix
尽管自Netflix以来我不得不说
built this Netflix started out with a
建立这个Netflix最初是
with another solution that they've built
他们建立的另一个解决方案
first which was called a skort and they
首先，这被称为sk鱼，他们
have replaced that with spinnaker and
用大三角帆代替了
taking all their learnings from Asgard
从阿斯加德学到的所有东西
and applied it here and for this
并在这里和这里应用
spinnaker version they started using
他们开始使用的大三角帆版本
spring boot and you might remember not
spring boot ，你可能记得没有
fixable as that's being used in spring
可修复的，因为在春季使用
cloud this kind of makes it full circle
使这种云浑圆
because now that fix is also using
因为现在该修复程序还在使用
spring to build their own applications
Spring 建立自己的应用程序
right they've been doing that for like
对，他们一直这样做是为了
coffee here already so that was pretty
这里已经有咖啡了，所以很漂亮
big news as well aside from Netflix you
除了Netflix之外，还有重大新闻
have obviously been contributing the
显然已经做出了贡献
most to this application this platform
对这个应用程序最重要的是这个平台
Google has been heavily invested in this
Google已为此投入巨资
as well if I'm not mistaken they've
如果我没记错的话
actually put 14 FTEs on it just to be
实际上只是放了14个FTE
building kubernetes supports and even
构建kubernetes支持甚至
much more features even the like support
更多功能甚至支持
for for App Engine for instance is also
例如，对于App Engine来说，
in there
在那里
so aside from Google Microsoft has
除了Google之外，Microsoft还有
contributes the azure support and
贡献天青的支持和
pivotal the car foundry support so this
关键的汽车铸造厂的支持，所以这
this is actually an entire ecosystem and
这实际上是整个生态系统
if you look at it right now it kind of
如果你现在看的话
supports all the major clouds and
支持所有主要云
there's actually more clouds coming and
实际上有更多的乌云降临，
so we're going to be using Azure for our
所以我们将使用Azure作为我们的
demo but it also perfectly works on
演示，但它也可以完美地工作
Google the CI system integration it kind
Google CI系统集成实物
of it really wants to integrate with CIS
它真的想与CIS集成
because it doesn't one or two builds
因为它没有一两个构建
right if you have your Jenkins or your
如果您有詹金斯人或
concourse or whatever you're using for
大厅或您正在使用的任何东西
CI then keep using that because it's
CI然后继续使用它，因为它
that specialized and continuous
持续专业化
integration and building your software
集成和构建软件
spinnaker doesn't care about that much
大三角帆并不那么在乎
it can bake images sure but it doesn't
它可以烘烤图像，但不能
it's not really focused on it it's
它不是真的专注于它
focused on having these strategic
专注于使这些战略
deployment pipelines for taking your
部署管道以获取您的
application that's built and then
构建的应用程序，然后
putting it in the cloud so we're gonna
把它放到云端，我们要
be using Travis and ours in our case
在我们的情况下使用Travis和我们的
here for for our CI monitoring we're
在这里进行CI监控
gonna be using data org for metrics
将使用数据组织进行指标
because we're gonna need metrics for
因为我们将需要以下指标
continuous for it these automated canary
这些自动金丝雀连续
analysis notifications you can send out
您可以发送的分析通知
notifications of course and you can have
通知课程，您可以
art
艺术
support which is kind of just a
支持，这只是一个
repository where you get your released
您发布的存储库
deliverable from right so this could be
从正确的交付，所以这可能是
docker could be just an HTTP call or s3
码头工人可能只是一个HTTP呼叫或s3
in our case we're gonna be using s3 on
在我们的情况下，我们将在s3上使用
Amazon so we're gonna be using a couple
亚马逊，所以我们要使用几个
of different services on different
不同服务上的不同
clouds right and there's no problem in
乌云密布，没有问题
doing that so there the spinnaker
那样做，大三角帆
platform has been contributed to the
平台已为
continuous delivery foundation which is
持续交付的基础是
a new foundation underneath a linux
Linux下的新基础
foundation so now it's completely part
基础，所以现在已经完全
of the Linux Foundation which is also
Linux Foundation的
pretty interesting so let me talk a bit
非常有趣，让我说一点
about what spinner can do right because
关于微调器可以做什么，因为
I've been talking about what spinnaker
我一直在谈论什么大三角帆
is but not necessarily why it's
是但不一定是为什么
interesting to us right what are these
对我们来说有趣的是什么
these new cutting-edge features right so
这些新的尖端功能就这样
when we go to the cloud what do we care
当我们上云时，我们在乎什么
about and basically when I go to teams
大概和我什么时候去团队
and I look at how they work they mostly
我看他们如何工作
have issues when they want to scale out
他们想要横向扩展时遇到问题
two different clouds or two different
两个不同的云或两个不同
regions so cloud deployment in general
区域，因此一般来说云部署
are pretty complex if you if you start
如果您开始的话，会非常复杂
simple then it's then it's okay but once
简单然后就可以了，但是一旦
you start pushing having multiple people
你开始推动有多个人
and multiple teams pushing multiple
和多个团队推动多个
changes over multiple different services
多种不同服务的转换
through multiple availability zones
通过多个可用区
multiple regions across different
跨越不同的多个区域
providers then this stuff becomes more
提供者，那么这东西变得更多
complex this becomes difficult because
复杂，这变得困难，因为
you got to know all your different
你必须知道你所有的不同
abstractions and all the different
抽象和所有不同
concepts of all the different clouds and
所有不同的云的概念和
you know most companies are focused on
你知道大多数公司都专注于
one provider that I know of like they
我认识的一个提供者喜欢他们
choose either or Google or Amazon right
选择Google或Amazon权利
but I don't think there's many companies
但我不认为有很多公司
that completely migrate to the cloud
完全迁移到云
right there's also something running
对了还有东西在跑
on-premise now it would be it would it
现在就可以了
would be kind of annoying to have your
拥有你会很烦
applications running on present
目前运行的应用程序
on-premise and in the cloud and not have
本地和云中，没有
a composite view across all these
所有这些的综合视图
different environments but especially if
不同的环境，但尤其是如果
you have dev acceptance education or
您接受过开发者接受教育或
whatever you call it and production
不管你叫它和生产
right even if you just use Amazon right
即使您只是使用亚马逊也可以
they have if you have a production
他们有，如果你有生产
Amazon and development Amazon they're
亚马逊及其发展中的亚马逊
probably different accounts right so if
可能是不同的帐户，所以如果
you want to get a view of
您想了解一下
whereas where's your application you're
而您的应用程序在哪里
gonna have to log into it the production
将不得不登录到生产
accounts to see it right or at least
认为正确或至少正确
that's of my knowledge so that's quite
据我所知，这相当
annoying and spinnaker offers this multi
烦人和大三角帆提供了这种多
foundation multi-cloud multi-region view
基础多云多区域视图
of your application just gives you in
您的应用程序只是让您
one page where's your application where
一页您的应用程序在哪里
does it live how many instances is it
它有多少个实例？
alive or not is it having issues or not
活着与否
and that's really pretty helpful if
如果这真的很有帮助
you're just a development team that
你只是一个开发团队
wants to see what's going on right aside
想看看旁边发生了什么
from there so this is the inventory that
从那里，这是库存
we talked about before right
我们之前谈到过
aside from this team's want to get an
除了这个团队想要获得
easy solution to do go to the cloud
轻松解决方案去云
right they want to have a paved road in
对，他们想在
the wilderness in the chaos of clap
拍手的混乱中的旷野
right so an easy pipeline that maybe
对，所以一个简单的管道可能
even pre-built as a template that really
甚至作为模板预先构建
helps teams to go to the clouds easy so
帮助团队轻松前往云端
that's also what spinnaker offers us
这也是大三角帆为我们提供的
it's it's easy for for teams to on board
这对于团队来说很容易
on this because it abstracts away all
在此上，因为它抽象了所有
the complexities of the clouds
云的复杂性
themselves and it gives you this easy
自己，它给你这么容易
path also a once you're actually in
路径实际上也是一次
production you want to be able to roll
您想要能够生产的产品
back quickly right so easy roll backs
快速返回正确的位置，因此容易回滚
are important right because you can come
很重要，因为你可以来
you can have as much speed as you want
您可以根据需要获得尽可能多的速度
right but even though you might have a
是的，但是即使您可能有一个
lot of confidence things do I still go
我仍然很自信
wrong and then you want to go back in an
错误，然后您想回去
easy way so you want to be able to go
简单的方法，所以你想去
back in time without having chaos right
时光倒流而没有混乱
and spinnaker office do this that's with
和大三角帆办公室做到这一点
one just one click of a button that you
只需单击一下按钮即可
could roll back of course if you have
如果有的话，当然可以回滚
database migrations you might want to
您可能想要进行数据库迁移
have a rollback database scripts or
具有回滚数据库脚本或
something like that right but aside from
这样的权利，但除了
that it tells you exactly what is going
它告诉你确切的情况
to do and why is that important it's
要做的事，为什么如此重要
because when we do row backs this is not
因为当我们做排背不是
something that we want to do in a very
我们非常想做的事情
this is not something that we're kind of
这不是我们的那种
happy about right this is mostly a
对这个很高兴，这主要是
stressful situation right we're mostly
压力很大的情况，我们主要是
under stress if we do roll backs so
在压力下，如果我们回滚的话
that's when we make mistakes and just
那是我们犯错的时候
making sure that we have a scripted way
确保我们有一种脚本化的方式
or like a provided way from spinnaker
或像大三角帆提供的方式
that tells you exactly the steps that
告诉您确切的步骤
are going to do is really a big help so
将要做的事确实有很大帮助，所以
I'm not gonna done with that but it's
我不会那样做，但是
just a click of a button and you can go
只需单击一个按钮，您就可以
back to any versions that you said that
回到您所说的任何版本
you still have some
你还有一些
now who knows this picture anyone from
现在谁知道这张照片的人
the crowd so a couple and and what is it
人群如此一对，这是什么
like when do you see this get up is down
就像你什么时候看到这个起床落下
yeah exactly right and there's normally
是的，完全正确，通常
not many people I think just here is
我想这里的人不多
most the most amount of people I
我最多的人
actually ever gotten in the talk so the
实际上曾经参与讨论，所以
idea is that github wants to make this
想法是github想要做到这一点
sound like it's impossible that it's
听起来这是不可能的
never happening right because unicorns
永远不会发生，因为独角兽
don't exist so when Caleb is down we
不存在，所以当迦勒倒下时，我们
want to make sure that you know the
想要确保您知道
blast radius is as small as possible
爆炸半径尽可能小
that hasn't as least amount of people
没有那么多的人
are impacted as possible so when you
尽可能受到影响，所以当您
deploy you need to make sure you deploy
部署您需要确保您部署
during a time frame when there's not
在没有的时候
many people online you know it's not a
很多人在线，你知道这不是一个
lot of traffic and also that you can
大量的流量，也可以
easily remember yet remediates sorry the
容易记住，但补救措施对不起
when when this actually goes down
当这实际上下降时
so having deployment windows and having
因此拥有部署窗口并拥有
keeping track of when your traffic is
跟踪您的流量何时
coming in is important for identifying
进场对于确定身份很重要
these and you can even link that with
这些，甚至可以将其与
when people are actually in the office
当人们实际上在办公室时
right because you might do this at night
对，因为您可能在晚上这样做
but then people are on call and it's not
但是后来有人在电话上，不是
really the same experience as when
真的和当初一样
you're actually in the office so
你实际上在办公室所以
netflix has actually integrated the the
netflix实际上已经整合了
traffic of their application that
他们的应用流量
they're currently deploying which could
他们目前正在部署
be different for each application and
每个应用程序都不同，并且
then link that to the deployment window
然后将其链接到部署窗口
so the idea is that you would prepare
所以想法是你会准备
everything upfront that's required for
预先需要的一切
doing your deployments up until the
进行部署直到
point where you're actually going to
指出您实际上要去的地方
switch the traffic right and at that
切换流量，然后
point you wait until you hit the
点你等到你打
appointment window and then you roll
约会窗口，然后滚动
forward all right so that's having that
转发所有的权利，所以有
as an automated solution it's pretty
作为自动化的解决方案
powerful of course when you deploy as
当您部署为
well you don't just want to you know
好吧，你不只是想知道
like bring everything down bring
像把一切都带下来
everything up right because you cannot
一切都正确，因为你不能
have downtime even things like Bluegreen
甚至有停机时间，例如Bluegreen
appointments might not be enough like
约会可能还不够
here you see an example of a Bluegreen
在这里，您可以看到一个蓝绿色的例子
deployment nothing's called a black
部署无所谓的黑色
which is pretty funny cuz that logo used
该徽标使用的是非常有趣的cuz
to be red and black but it's red and
是红色和黑色，但它是红色和
white anyway so jokes on them I suppose
无论如何都是白色，所以我想对他们开玩笑
Bluegreen gives brings up the next
蓝绿色放弃带来了下一个
version next to the first version right
第一个版本旁边的版本
so you have version 1 version 2 both
所以你都拥有版本1和版本2
both ready to serve right and version 1
均已准备好投放权利和版本1
is it's just
只是
all the traffic the load balancer on top
所有流量，负载均衡器位于顶部
of it can easily switch just to this
它可以很容易地切换到这个
version too and then have all the
版本，然后拥有所有
traffic routed to version 2 if there's
如果有
any issue version 1 is still running you
任何问题版本1仍在运行
can just flip the switch in the load
只需轻按负载中的开关即可
bouncer and you'd have all traffic
保镖，您将拥有所有流量
routers two versions one so you wouldn't
路由器两个版本一个，所以您不会
have that it would be an easy rollback
拥有一个简单的回滚
Yeah right so it's not really something
是的，所以这不是真的
that that would be difficult to remove
那将很难去除
remediated however you would have all
补救，但是您将拥有全部
your users exposed to this downtime or
您的用户遭受了这种停机或
to this issue right that you would have
您将拥有的这个问题
at version 2 you can fix that by doing
在版本2中，您可以通过执行以下操作来解决此问题
rolling Bluegreen or rolling right back
滚动蓝绿色或向右滚动
in this case where you wouldn't have a
在这种情况下，您将没有
full switchover but you would have it
完全切换，但您会拥有
gradually by bringing up an instance up
通过提出一个实例逐渐
at a time and an instance down of the
在一个时间和一个实例下来
previous version at a time or you could
一次使用以前的版本，或者您可以
do some sophisticated load balancing
做一些复杂的负载平衡
which routes a portion of the traffic
路由一部分流量
right with each step that you take you
每走一步就正确
would either do a manual verification
要么进行手动验证
step a validation whether this would
进行验证是否会
work or not or you would have some kind
工作与否，否则你会有某种
of a smoke test or something
抽烟测试之类的
normally this doesn't go really deep or
通常这不会很深入或
it's not really a sophisticated test now
现在还不是一个复杂的测试
canary canary testing takes it one step
金丝雀金丝雀测试迈出了第一步
further and the difference with rolling
进一步和滚动的区别
Bluegreen is that it has this automated
蓝绿色是它具有这种自动化
canary analysis in between each step so
在每个步骤之间进行金丝雀分析
when you're routing traffic to more and
当您将流量路由到更多
more users you're going to check whether
更多的用户，您要检查是否
the new version acts as the acts the
新版本充当行为
same as the previous version or even
与以前的版本相同甚至
better right and if that's the case
更好的权利，如果是这样
you're going to scale up if it's if it's
如果是的话，您将扩大规模
acting worse it's going to scale down
表现更糟它将缩小
right it's going to roll back so that's
正确，它将回滚，所以
kind of the idea here and the way it's
这里的想法及其方式
doing it it's looking at metrics this
这样做是在看指标
this could be system metrics of course
这当然可以是系统指标
but it could also be business metrics so
但也可能是业务指标
you could have for instance if you have
例如，如果您有
an e-commerce website you could be
您可能是一个电子商务网站
selling shoes for instance right if all
例如卖鞋，如果有的话
of a sudden shoes are not being sold
突然没有出售鞋子
anymore
不再
right then you might have an issue it
对，那么你可能有一个问题
with your website with your deployments
与您的网站一起进行部署
right and that you can actually have
对，你实际上可以拥有
that as a metric that you want to take
作为您要采用的指标
into account right so just looking at
考虑到正确的，所以只是看着
the difference in whatever portion of
在任何部分的差异
your user base is has as access to the
您的用户群可以访问
new version can give you this
新版本可以给你这个
information to roll out or to
要推出或发布的信息
go back hey that's the idea we're going
回去嘿，这就是我们要去的想法
to be actually doing this in our demo so
实际在我们的演示中这样做
automation is key here you can't you
自动化是关键，你不能
can't do this manually and spinnaker
不能手动做到这一点和大三角帆
kind of tries to automate all this stuff
尝试使所有这些东西自动化
for you like when you automate
当您喜欢自动化时
continuous deployment
持续部署
there are contains every pipeline's then
有包含每个管道的
normally what you do is in Jenkins for
通常你在詹金斯（Jenkins）做
instance if you who's using Jenkins
如果您正在使用詹金斯
who's not using Jenkins all right oh
谁不使用詹金斯
it's so fair amount so most people are
这么多钱，所以大多数人
using Jenkins right you sure you're
使用Jenkins对，您确定
right these scripts right right the
正确执行这些脚本，正确执行
groovy scripts that will do this stuff
groovy脚本将执行此操作
these scripts could be using libraries
这些脚本可能正在使用库
right which could be tested separately
可以单独测试的权利
but mostly or people when people
但大多数还是当人
actually write this stuff the moment
马上写这些东西
they are testing it is when they're
他们正在测试当他们
running the pipeline right so this is
正确运行管道，所以这是
not really something which is super
真的不是超级东西
robust right it's kind of trial and
健壮的权利，这是一种尝试，
error a lot of a lot of the times so I'm
很多时候都犯错了，所以我
having something which is built in a
有一些内置的东西
platform for you with these blocks that
这些块为您提供平台
you can compose that are tested by the
您可以撰写经
community and improved by the community
社区，并由社区改善
it's much more powerful right because I
这是更强大的权利，因为我
think of all the people who are doing
想想所有正在做的人
these Jenkins scripts a lot of us are
这些我们很多人的詹金斯脚本
just doing the same work we're just
只是做同样的工作
writing the same scripts right we're
写同样的脚本吧
just doing it all over and over again so
只是一遍又一遍地做，所以
having this as part of the platform is a
将其作为平台的一部分是
real benefit so here you have one of the
真正的好处，所以在这里您可以
examples one one possible pipeline you
示例一个可能的管道
clip one which is a deployment to
剪辑一个部署
production one it has it so it looks in
生产一有它所以它看起来
the test environments it's it finds the
在测试环境中找到
image from of it from the test
来自测试的图像
environment and it uses that to deploy a
环境，它使用它来部署
canary so the this is the new version
金丝雀，所以这是新版本
right so it's the poor is the canary
对，所以穷人是金丝雀
then it's waiting 30 minutes because it
然后等待30分钟，因为
wants to get some metrics first from the
想要首先从
people who are composed to the canary
组成金丝雀的人
and then eventually if the canary works
然后最终如果金丝雀起作用
fine then you can have a manual cut over
很好，那么您可以手动进行切割
so you can have a manual approval but
所以您可以手动批准
that you say okay this feels good for us
你说好，这对我们来说感觉很好
and this is also going to be in our demo
这也将在我们的演示中
and then once that's once the canary is
然后曾经是金丝雀
verified then you can have a Bluegreen
经过验证，您可以拥有Bluegreen
deployment to production because you
部署到生产中，因为您
don't want any downtime right any one
不想让任何人停机
you might want to have this rolling if
你可能想让这个滚动
you really want to and then eventually
你真的想要，然后最终
this is deployed you want to tear down
这是您想要拆除的部署
the canary after two
两点后的金丝雀
hours right well you tear down the
正确的时间，你把
canary anyway two hours then use Troy
反正金丝雀两个小时，然后使用特洛伊
production right so canary you can just
生产权如此金丝雀就可以
get rid of right away so this is a
立即摆脱掉，所以这是一个
possible pipeline that you could build
您可以建立的可能管道
now all of these steps are provided by
现在所有这些步骤都由
spinnaker and let's just look into the
大三角帆，让我们看看
blue green one right
蓝绿色一右
what is entails so spinnaker does all
这意味着什么，所以大三角帆可以做所有的事情
this stuff so a blue green deployments
这样的东西，所以蓝绿色的部署
step or a stage for spinnaker there's a
三角帆的一个步骤或一个阶段
lot of steps which which have a lot of
很多步骤，其中有很多
tasks and a lot of operations so in this
任务和很多操作，所以在此
case it does like a deploy in default
如果它确实像默认部署
and then is shrinking the cluster the
然后缩小集群
previous cluster disabling it and
先前的集群禁用了它，并且
scaling down and a disabled of the
缩小比例并禁用
cluster actually does it determines the
集群实际上是否确定
help provider disabling the cluster
帮助提供商禁用集群
itself monitoring it forcing the cache
本身对其进行监视，从而强制缓存
refresh waiting for the disabled and
刷新等待残疾人和
enforcing it again and then the disabled
再次执行，然后禁用
of the cluster has a couple of
集群中有几个
operations which are low-level
低级操作
operations right so it's changing the
操作正确，因此它正在改变
the forwarding rules the target pools is
目标池的转发规则是
removing the actual instance so all this
删除实际实例，所以这一切
stuff is being done for you now of
现在正在为您做的事情
course you could do this yourself as
当然你可以自己做
well in the Jenkins script right this is
在詹金斯脚本中很好，这是
possible but I mean why would you even
可能，但我的意思是你为什么会
want to do that right especially if all
想做到这一点，特别是如果所有
this stuff is very specific for each
这些东西对于每个人来说都是非常具体的
cloud provider but spinnaker gives us an
云提供商，但大三角帆给了我们一个
abstraction layer of concepts where we
我们在概念的抽象层
don't have to worry about the specifics
不必担心细节
of these clouds this enables us to
这些云使我们能够
deploy to multiple clouds in the same
部署到同一云中的多个云
fashion by the way so this is a very
顺便说一句时尚，这是一个非常
important part here of our continuous
这是我们持续不断的重要组成部分
deployment or the contains the delivery
部署或包含交付
solution is that automation should be
解决方案是自动化应该
built in right so why we do when we
内置正确的，所以我们为什么要做
actually deploy something then we want
实际部署一些我们想要的东西
to make sure that we use information
确保我们使用信息
from the operational side so canary
从操作方面看，金丝雀
deployments canary testing takes metrics
部署金丝雀测试采用指标
from production and makes decisions
从生产和决策
while deploying based on those metrics
根据这些指标进行部署时
right so it's taking information from
对，因此它正在从中获取信息
the operational side into the deployment
部署中的操作方面
pipeline and of course once it's
管道，当然一旦
deployed we want to make sure that we
部署后，我们要确保我们
want to be able to trace back to
希望能够追溯到
whatever happens during a canary release
金丝雀释放期间发生的一切
or anything like that when something is
或类似的东西
actually not working on production and
实际上不从事生产和
being able to roll back really easily
能够非常轻松地回滚
really it has this up I mean it benefits
真的有它，我的意思是它有益
from this operational
从这个操作
integration so now I'm gonna be talking
整合，所以现在我要说的是
about Canary Birds Allah I've already
关于我已经有的金丝雀鸟阿拉
mentioned it quite a lot and we're going
提到了很多，我们要去
to be killing some birds I don't have
杀死一些我没有的鸟
any birds bird lovers here no bird
任何鸟类鸟类爱好者这里没有鸟类
lovers okay one over there so I have a
恋人可以在那边，所以我有一个
special slide for you
特别的幻灯片给你
I have some canary birds for you you
我有几只金丝雀给你
know just to just have I mean appreciate
知道只是想拥有我的意思
them a bit you know because they're
他们有点你知道，因为他们是
looking really cute right but we're
看起来真的很可爱，但是我们
gonna be killing a lot of them so I hope
将会杀死很多人，所以我希望
you don't mind and okay so that's over
你不在乎，好了，就结束了
with so it's a canary analysis looks
因此，这是金丝雀分析的样子
like this right it has a stage a stage
像这样的权利，它有一个阶段
which has a couple of different analysis
其中有一些不同的分析
results so you just analyze what's going
结果，所以您只需分析正在发生的事情
on in your canary and then you get a
在你的金丝雀上，然后你得到一个
score for it and this score is based on
得分，该得分基于
the metrics and but are you improved or
指标，但您是否有所改善或
whether you but you have the same or
无论您是否拥有相同的
whether you actually have a worse result
你是否真的有更糟糕的结果
right and when the score is high enough
对并且分数足够高时
then you roll for it
然后你为它滚动
so just to give you an indication
所以只是给你一个指示
Netflix has a score of at least 95
Netflix的分数至少为95
percent before it moves forward and they
前进之前的百分比，他们
run their Canaries for about like four
运行他们的金丝雀大约四个
hours at least or something
至少几个小时
sometimes it's days that they're running
有时候是他们跑步的日子
their Canaries just to make sure that
他们的金丝雀只是为了确保
the blast radius is always as small as
爆炸半径总是小到
possible right in this case we're not
在这种情况下可能的权利，我们不是
gonna be doing this for four hours
要做四个小时
because I suppose you want to see some
因为我想你想看一些
other interesting stuff today and so
今天还有其他有趣的东西
we're gonna do it for six minutes of
我们要做六分钟
course the results will be a little bit
当然结果会有点
you know less impactful but I hope it
您知道影响较小，但我希望
gets the message across so it looks a
传达信息，所以看起来
bit like this
像这样
you have your metrics from from your
您有自己的指标
brown release which is the baseline and
棕色释放是基线和
metrics from the the blue release which
蓝色版本中的指标
is the canary and you can see that in
是金丝雀，你可以看到
this case it's a failure because it's
在这种情况下是失败的，因为
only 58% score right that's the score
只有58％的分数是对的
it's not really great so we're gonna be
真的不是很好，所以我们会成为
seeing something similar I hope right if
看到类似的东西，我希望是
everything goes well now aside from that
除此之外，现在一切都很好
you can also integrate chaos monkeys of
您还可以整合混乱的猴子
course this was confirmed comes from
当然这被确认来自
Netflix and Netflix are notorious for
Netflix和Netflix臭名昭著
their chaos monkeys right they have the
他们的混乱猴子对，他们有
simian army is anyone well I'm not gonna
猿人军是谁，我不会
ask but like not many people are
问，但好像没有多少人
probably going to or actually do in
可能去或实际上做
chaos testing currently I think
我认为目前测试混乱
but it is possible even if it's just on
但即使它刚打开也有可能
an acceptance environment or something
接受环境等
you can integrate chaos chaos monkeys
你可以整合混乱的猴子
right into your pipeline if it's if
直接进入您的管道，如果
someone's unfamiliar with chaos monkeys
某人不熟悉混沌猴子
it's like having monkeys in production
就像在生产猴子
pulling plugs right and seeing
拔插头，看到
everything everything's still fine I
一切都还好我
mean the last part is sometimes
表示最后一部分有时
overlooked we're just you know you just
忽略了我们就是你认识你而已
implement chaos monkeys and then don't
实施混乱的猴子，然后不要
care about them I've seen that before
关心他们，我以前见过
which is a bit dangerous anyway so you
反正有点危险所以你
can do that if you want to so this is
可以这样做，如果你想这样做
the story about having speed and
关于速度和速度的故事
confidence right so spinnaker really
信心对，所以大三角帆真的
tries to make it possible to ramp up
试图使其加速
speed and still have safety right which
速度并仍然拥有安全权
is sometimes contradict contradictory
有时矛盾
right and the way that it does that is
正确的方法和方法是
making sure you have automated rollbacks
确保您有自动回滚
that if things go wrong that you can
如果出现问题，您可以
easily roll back that you have
轻松回滚您拥有的
deployment windows chaos monkeys
部署Windows混乱的猴子
deployment strategies and automated
部署策略和自动化
scenario analysis and that's what we've
情景分析，这就是我们要做的
been talking about right but also it
一直在谈论正确但也
offers some more features with I'm not
提供更多功能，而我不是
which I'm not going to show
我不会显示
unfortunately cuz we don't have enough
不幸的是，因为我们没有足够的
time but we have cluster locking if you
时间，但如果您有集群锁定
have multiple pipelines acting on the
有多个作用于
same cluster or the same server group
同一集群或同一服务器组
that I give you an intended results
我给你一个预期的结果
right so you can lock that cluster so
对，所以您可以锁定该群集，以便
that all other pipelines are our health
所有其他管道都是我们的健康
until this first one actually finishes
直到第一个完成
you can have traffic guards now this
你现在可以有交通警卫了
stuff can move really fast right you can
东西可以快速移动，就可以
have deployments going on all the time
一直在进行部署
right and then there might be some
对，然后可能会有一些
scenario that you haven't thought of
您从未想到的场景
start off that deletes the last server
开始删除最后一个服务器
group right in some kind of strange
在某种奇怪的群体权利
combination of strategies now you can
现在可以结合策略
have a traffic guard that ensures that
有一个交通警卫，以确保
whatever you do in your pipelines you're
无论您在管道中做什么，
never going to remove the last server
永远不会删除最后一个服务器
group because then you have obvious
组，因为那么你有明显的
on-time right
准时的权利
so you can have that easily implemented
这样您就可以轻松实现
as well manual judgments we're gonna
以及手动判断
have a manual judgment of Python as well
对Python也有手动判断
where we can still say okay I want to
我们仍然可以说好，我想
accept this or I want to continue or I
接受这个，或者我想继续，或者我
don't want to continue and why is this
不想继续，这是为什么
important
重要
it's kind of the difference between
这之间的区别是
continuous delivery and continue the
持续交付并继续
problem right is that manual cutover
问题是手动交接
right and that's still important why
对，那仍然很重要
because it's the gut feeling of humans
因为这是人类的直觉
the computer doesn't have that right a
电脑没有正确的权限
computer can never know about the
电脑永远不会知道
contextual things that happen in your
您的情境中发生的事
organization but they might know as part
组织，但他们可能知道
of it but not a full picture it could be
它，但可能不完整
that you
那你
you've just been informed by your
您刚刚被您的通知
colleague that there might be a firewall
同事可能有防火墙
change somewhere that might impact your
改变可能会影响您的地方
deployment right like you might know
就像您可能知道的那样进行部署
that but a computer might not right so
那但是一台电脑可能不正确
it's still having that manual that human
它仍然拥有该手册，
intervention there is still an important
干预仍然很重要
step and it's just a red button that you
步骤，这只是一个红色按钮
can again you can press if you want to
可以再次按一下是否要
continue right so it's very cheap so
继续吧，所以很便宜，所以
that's also in there of course
当然也在那里
conditional pipelines and staged
有条件的管道和分段
executions likely to be more dynamic and
执行可能更动态，
of course have more than notifications
当然不只是通知
as well so go fast with safety that's
同样，安全性也要快速提高
kind of a model of spinnaker here right
有点像大三角帆的模型
that's when we go want to go as fast as
那就是当我们想走得最快的时候
possible to production but still have
可以生产但仍然有
confidence so what's coming up for
信心，这是怎么回事
spinnaker there I'm so spinnaker is
我在那里的大三角帆是
building a CLI for pipeline it's code so
建立管道的CLI就是代码
you can easily write writes your
您可以轻松地写写您的
pipelines that's code
代码的管道
you can already do that currently but
您目前已经可以这样做，但是
you can also do that through the CLI
您也可以通过CLI进行操作
declarative CD so instead of defining a
声明性CD，而不是定义一个
pipeline that like we saw an automation
就像我们看到自动化的管道
example for you can say I have an
你可以说我有一个例子
application I want to deploy that to
我想将其部署到的应用程序
death I want to deploy it to production
死亡我想将其部署到生产中
after that and I want to do that in a
之后，我想在一个
canary fashion right figure it out for
金丝雀时尚权找出来
me and then spin your spinnaker is going
我然后旋转你的大三角帆去
to make sure that just like with
确保与
kubernetes where you define an end state
定义结束状态的Kubernetes
that you also gonna reach that end state
你也将达到最终状态
of your pipeline which would be pretty
你的管道，这将是漂亮的
cool right you don't have to write any
很酷的权利，您不必写任何
code anymore also support for artifacts
代码不再支持工件
which is already there more cloud
已经有更多的云了
professional platforms so Alibaba cloud
专业平台让阿里云
if anyone knows that is actually it's
如果有人知道这实际上是
actually work on the way now to support
实际在支持的方式上工作
that and OpenShift has started has now
并且OpenShift已经开始
stalled a bit but might be picked up in
停了一下，但可能会在
the future again I'm also more
未来又是我
comprehensive provisioning support first
全面的配置支持优先
canary stages you're gonna see that we
金丝雀阶段，你会看到我们
are going to bring up our baseline and
将提出我们的基准
our and our new version or canary next
我们和我们的新版本或金丝雀下一步
to each other aside from the production
除了生产彼此
versions right we can do that also like
版本正确，我们也可以做到
in a more declarative way so that you
以更具声明性的方式，以便您
don't have to worry about that and then
不必担心，然后
eventually we're gonna have to destroy
最终我们将不得不摧毁
that that can also be homemade and then
那也可以是自制的，然后
there's there's a whole community behind
后面有整个社区
this right and there's even conference
这个权利，甚至有会议
is about spinnaker so it's definitely a
是关于大三角帆的，所以绝对是
growing thing and more I mean all the
越来越多的东西，我的意思是所有
cloud providers that are kind of the big
大型云提供商
ones are right now
那些现在
for it but there's more and more
为此，但越来越多
informations coming so I think that's
信息来了，所以我认为
enough for the slides right although I
足够的幻灯片，虽然我
do have some interesting slides left for
确实还有一些有趣的幻灯片
the demo right so the demo here is going
演示正确，所以这里的演示正在进行
to be on Azure with its pivotal Cloud
借助其关键云在Azure上
Foundry pas you'd like to call that
您想要称呼的铸造厂
running on Azure we also have PKS which
在Azure上运行，我们还有PKS
is kubernetes running next to it it
kubernetes在它旁边运行吗
Spinnaker's report on that kubernetes
大三角帆关于kubernetes的报告
and it's then going to push apps to
然后将应用推送到
Cloud Foundry so it's kind of this joint
Cloud Foundry就是这种联合
world right I try to get as many
世界上的权利，我试图得到尽可能多的
different clouds in there as possible
尽可能有不同的云
just to make a point of course this
只是为了说明这一点
could all fail really badly so we're
可能真的失败很严重，所以我们
gonna see about that but the demo has a
会看到的，但演示有一个
story behind it does anyone know Rick
背后的故事有人知道里克
and Morty oh yeah you know some
和莫蒂哦，是的，你知道一些
conferences that go just like one or two
像一两个会议一样的会议
but this is this is amazing so you might
但这是很棒的，所以你可能
all know this one right it's this is
都知道这是对的
pretty funny cartoon and we're gonna be
非常有趣的卡通，我们将成为
working with a green and a blue version
使用绿色和蓝色版本
and our green version our protagonist
而我们的绿色版本是我们的主角
here is pickle Rick you know if you've
这是泡菜里克，你知道吗
seen the episode Rick turns himself into
看到里克把自己变成情节
a pickle to avoid going to Family
泡菜避免去家庭
Therapy because he really hates that but
疗法，因为他真的很讨厌，但是
then you know things happen and he rolls
然后你知道事情发生了，他滚了
into the sewer and has to fight the
进入下水道，必须与
fight against rats and cockroaches and
对抗老鼠和蟑螂
eventually he comes out victorious so
最终他取得了胜利，所以
he's a really strong glue green version
他是一个很强的胶绿色版本
right really predictable really strong
对，真的可以预测，真的很强大
really stable version right nothing can
真正稳定的版本，没什么可以
go wrong with this version you know it
这个版本出了错你知道
will always persevere now so this is our
会一直坚持下去，所以这就是我们
green version then on the other hand we
绿色版本，另一方面，我们
have our blue or blue antagonist right
有我们的蓝色或蓝色反对者权利
this is our blue version that doesn't
这是我们的蓝色版本
play well all right I mean initially it
好吧，好吧，我是说开始
might sound like it's a good idea
听起来好像是个好主意
because it's a genie in a box who acted
因为它是一个盒子里的精灵
who exists only to solve the task at
谁只是为了解决任务而存在
hand right so that's great right but the
右手，所以这是伟大的权利，但
thing is if he doesn't succeed in that
问题是如果他没有成功
task then he grows old and he doesn't
然后他变老了，但他没有
wanna grow old he just want to disappear
想变老，他只想消失
again right so he gets aggressive
再次正确，所以他变得好斗
because he really wants to solve that
因为他真的很想解决
task he's so he's a really dangerous
他的任务很危险
chaotic and unstable Bluford so we
混乱和不稳定的Bluford，所以我们
probably want to roll that back right
可能想将其回滚
right you get it like blue green
对，你得到它像蓝绿色
deployment kind of thing
部署类的东西
so to give you some more feedback about
为了给您更多有关
the Mystics thing you know I have a
你知道我有一个神秘主义者的东西
whole storyline here I'm gonna go
整个故事情节我要走了
through it really fast so he was created
通过它真的很快，所以他被创造了
to solve the task of making this guy
解决做这个家伙的任务
golf better but he can't golf so that's
打高尔夫球更好，但是他不能打高尔夫球，所以
really hard so after a while he starts
真的很难，所以过了一会儿他开始
spawning new new versions of himself
产生自己的新新版本
right to help him but they just can't
帮助他的权利，但他们却做不到
make it work because this guy can't golf
使它起作用，因为这个家伙不会打高尔夫球
right so they all grow old and they all
对，所以他们都变老了，他们都
start being aggressive they start
开始积极进取
attacking people right because you
攻击别人是正确的，因为你
really really want to make sure that
真的很想确保
this guy can play golf because they all
这个家伙可以打高尔夫，因为他们都
can disappear them so eventually this is
可以消失他们，所以最终这是
super dangerous right so this is our
超级危险的权利，所以这是我们的
story I hope this demo will be much more
故事，我希望这个演示会更多
interesting now now that we need see
现在很有趣，我们需要看看
them see this story so for the demo you
他们看到了这个故事，所以对于演示您
can participate as well right you can go
可以参加也可以参加
to this this address and see our current
到这个地址，看看我们当前
version in production you can even take
您甚至可以制作的生产版本
a picture of the QR code I don't know if
不知道QR码的图片
this actually ever works has anyone got
这实际上曾经奏效过有人
any success with this
任何成功
works
作品
is it the server error are you kidding
是服务器错误吗？
me oh my god okay it works you have to
我，我的天哪，好的，你必须
refresh oh yeah yeah okay so this is a
刷新哦，是的，好的，这是一个
live demo so it might indeed not work
现场演示，所以它可能确实不起作用
we're gonna see about that
我们会看到的
so while you're all doing that and
所以当你都这样做的时候
trying to get rid of the servers right
试图摆脱服务器的权利
I'm gonna introduce vinegar to you as a
我要向你介绍醋
live demo and so here you can see
现场演示，所以在这里您可以看到
spinnaker running on PKS which is
在PKS上运行的大三角帆是
kubernetes and it currently has Def and
kubernetes，目前具有Def和
production so if you look at them you
生产，所以如果你看着他们
have one instance of version 13 because
有一个版本13的实例，因为
I've been trying this a lot right the
我一直在尝试这个
13th version and then on production
第13版，然后生产
there's version 2 currently running it
当前正在运行版本2
has four instances right four instances
有四个实例，四个实例
so if you look at the details you can
因此，如果您查看详细信息，则可以
actually see the instance IDs and the
实际看到实例ID和
zone and the weather they're up and
区域和天气，以及
they're all saying they're up so there
他们都说他们已经起来了
shouldn't be a problem
应该不是问题
I hope so
希望如此
we can go to the load balancers and load
我们可以去负载均衡器和负载
balancers basically in cloud foundry
平衡器基本上在云铸造中
they're just routes right so I can go to
他们就是正确的路线，所以我可以去
the route for this one I can click it as
我可以点击的路线
well here so it gives me this
好吧，这给了我
integration as well and this is my green
集成以及这就是我的绿色
version right it's pickle Ricky so it's
版本对，是泡菜Ricky，所以
pretty obvious right to that screen ok
该屏幕相当明显的权利
so then on production let's take a look
那么在生产上让我们看一下
what's happening on production on
生产中发生了什么
production I've got the green version as
生产我有绿色版本作为
well so everything's fine
好吧，一切都很好
you know no problem at all now we're
你完全不知道现在我们
gonna change that right so I'm going to
要改变这个权利，所以我要
make a change in my application now I'm
现在在我的应用程序中进行更改
having patience super sophisticated bro
有耐心的超级老兄
hot spring i/o so I decided to make a
spring i/o ，所以我决定做一个
very sophisticated spring ayo let's
非常精致的春季ayo让我们
bring boots demo right so we have a
带来靴子演示正确，所以我们有一个
spring spring good application which has
春暖花开的好应用
a controller right and that controller
控制器权和该控制器
it points to a view pickle rig which is
它指向一个视图泡菜钻机
a template which is an HTML page right
模板是HTML页面
so it's super sophisticated right I can
所以我可以做到
change this view and then it will go to
更改此视图，然后它将转到
musics right but we're not just gonna do
音乐没错，但我们不仅会做
that because that would be too simple
那是因为那太简单了
right
对
we're going to add some chaos because
我们将添加一些混乱，因为
musics are uncontrollable you know there
音乐是无法控制的，你知道那里
there's a very dangerous it's a very
有一个非常危险的
dangerous application at that point so
那时的危险应用
I'm gonna change this to me see
我要改变这个给我看看
mystics and I'm going to add some chaos
神秘主义者，我要添加一些混乱
now what does this chaos do you might
现在你可能会发生什么混乱
already see it's doing a sweep so
已经看到它正在扫一扫，所以
randomly it's sleeping 400 milliseconds
随机睡眠400毫秒
already right so there is some an
已经对了，所以有一些
uncontrollable data because this is
无法控制的数据，因为这是
constantly changing right every request
不断改变每一个要求
that I do you will have a little bit of
我做你会有点
that hundred milliseconds
那一百毫秒
now the chaos that I'll add will change
现在我要添加的混乱将会改变
this although it's not predictable
尽管这是不可预测的
because it's always it always has the
因为它总是具有
random the random stuff on top of it
将随机的东西随机放在它上面
there should be a trend right and that's
应该有正确的趋势，那就是
what we want to see in our in our matrix
我们想在矩阵中看到的
you want to see a trend that this is
你想看到一个趋势，这是
actually increased so just adding like
实际上增加了，所以增加像
50 milliseconds not being too dramatic
50毫秒不太剧烈
about this should already give us a
关于这个应该已经给我们了
clear a clear impact so I'm going to
清除明显的影响，所以我要
change this so add it chaos so I'm
改变这个，所以加上混乱，所以我
adding chaos right I'm doing this the
添加混乱权，我正在这样做
more sophisticated way should get help
更复杂的方法应该获得帮助
right because I mean IntelliJ is should
对，因为我是说IntelliJ应该
be overkill right so we have to wait a
太过正确了，所以我们必须等待
little bit because now my Travis
有点因为现在我的特拉维斯
pipeline should kick off at any moment
管道应随时启动
this could take a while because it's
这可能需要一段时间，因为
pulling but yeah eventually it's going
拉，但是的，最终它将
to do that so let's take a take a look
为此，让我们来看看
at the pipeline itself right so my
在管道本身上，所以我的
pipeline here has a deploy to dev stage
这里的管道有一个部署到开发阶段
at the Poti prod stage which will do a
在Poti产品阶段，
canary deployment and clean up the
金丝雀部署并清理
canary right so if actually the PM
金丝雀对，所以如果实际上PM
dictionary will be automated as well you
字典也会自动执行
won't have to worry about that but for
不必担心，但是
now buts so something that I do as a
现在却如此，我作为
separate pipeline now the deploy tube
分开的管道现在部署管
dev if you take a look at how its
开发人员，如果您看看它的
configured the configuration here it's
在这里配置了配置
basically looking at Travis because it
基本上看特拉维斯，因为它
has integration for Travis it's looking
与Travis集成，正在寻找
at the Travis CI master that I'm using
在我正在使用的Travis CI master上
and a job spinnaker demo which is you
和一个大三角帆演示是你
know this this despite my visible so
尽管我可见所以知道这一点
this could be a Jenkins thing as well
这也可能是詹金斯的事
it's actually a lot of things that you
实际上，你有很多东西
can integrate here so Jenkins a worker
可以在这里整合，让詹金斯成为一名工人
another pipeline pops up webhook a cron
另一个管道弹出webhook cron
job docker registry so you can also
作业docker注册表，因此您也可以
publish your darker instance to dr.
将较暗的实例发布给博士。
registry and then have that picked up
注册表，然后拿起
from there so that's pretty
从那里，这很漂亮
straightforward so our build while our
简单明了，所以我们的构建同时
build is going let's take a look at the
构建即将进行，让我们来看看
next step
下一步
so the deployment here let's
所以这里的部署
look at that so deployment will deploy
看一下，这样部署就会部署
to the cluster Rick and Morty death so
导致瑞克和莫蒂死亡
in the Deaf environments right and it
在聋哑环境中，它
will do Highlander strategy
将做汉兰达策略
who knows about Highlander strategy I
谁知道我的汉兰达策略
mean what could it possibly mean anyone
意味着什么可能意味着任何人
has any idea there can only be one right
有任何想法只能有一个权利
yeah so it's going to go in in the dev
是的，所以它将在开发中
environment and it's going to take this
环境，这需要
tour it's going to cut off all the heads
巡回演出将切断所有人的注意力
of all the other instances right so it's
在所有其他实例中，所以
gonna make sure that your deployment is
确保您的部署是
the only one alive right it sounds very
听起来唯一活着的权利
dramatic but wait until we get to the
戏剧性的，但是等到我们到达
canary stage so so this is kind of
金丝雀阶段，所以这是一种
what's going to happen you can just
将会发生什么，你可以
pretty easily point it to Jeff and then
轻松地将其指向Jeff，然后
select the strategy we can also of
选择我们也可以的策略
course take a strategy like a Bluegreen
当然采取像蓝绿这样的策略
strategy which does it a little bit more
可以做到的策略
kindly right or no strategy at all or
善意的权利或根本没有策略，或者
your own strategies oh yeah one thing I
你自己的策略哦，是的，我有一件事
almost forgot there's also the artifact
差点忘了还有神器
that we're getting from s3 so I'm just
我们从s3获得，所以我只是
gonna look at my s3 repository or bucket
要看我的s3储存库或存储桶
and I'm going to pick up whatever is
我要去接什么
being built there right and Travis tells
被建造在那里，特拉维斯告诉
me which one to take so Travis has now
我要带哪个，所以特拉维斯现在有
finished right it's green so that part
正确完成，它是绿色的，所以那部分
at least works and this one is now
至少有效，现在这个
deploying and if we now look at our
部署，如果我们现在来看一下
infrastructure and we get rid of the
基础设施，我们摆脱了
prop thing you see that in dev now you
你现在在开发中看到的道具
have over here now you have version 14
在这里，现在您有版本14
being spun up so version 14 14 is now
正在旋转，因此版本14 14现在
currently disabled because it's still
当前被禁用，因为它仍然
starting portion the 13 is still running
起始部分13仍在运行
now if we refresh and you can also
现在，如果我们刷新，您也可以
participate in this first so the Deaf
首先参加这个聋人
one right then now you see Mike Ploog
一个，然后现在您会看到Mike Ploog
version right and you know it's musics
版本正确，你知道这是音乐
right pretty obvious so this is the blue
对，很明显，所以这是蓝色
version and it might be that we still
版本，可能是我们仍然
have a little bit of a green version no
有一点绿色版本
I don't think so because the Highlander
我不这么认为，因为汉兰达
kicked in you know it just destroys the
踢进你知道这只会摧毁
older version so as you can see here
您可以在此处看到较旧的版本
version 13 is now stopped working you
版本13现在停止工作了
know it's now the disables right so
知道现在是残疾人士吧
that's that's working that's good you
那就是工作对你有好处
know part of the story already makes
知道故事的一部分已经使
sense so we are disabling the cluster
因此，我们正在禁用集群
let me just zoom out a little bit there
让我在那里放大一点
we go and then like we are deploying
我们去，然后就像我们正在部署
first then we
首先我们
stabling the old cluster and we are
稳定旧集群，我们
shrinking the old cluster eventually
最终缩小旧集群
right so that's that's basically
对，那基本上就是
underway what's going to happen next
进行中接下来会发生什么
is that it's going to deploy to
是要部署到
production right away so we just be
立即生产，所以我们只是
validated in in def it's fine just go
在def中验证过就可以了
ahead and deploy normally you would have
提前部署，通常情况下
some more stages in there right so this
还有更多的阶段，所以这
configuration here it just looks at the
这里的配置只是看
previous pipeline whether it was
以前的管道是否
successful and it was successful so it's
成功而成功，所以
gonna kick it off and then it's going to
要开始，然后它将
deploy a baseline and deploy canary now
部署基准并立即部署canary
why do we deploy a baseline you might
我们为什么要部署基准
ask right because you already have
问对了，因为你已经有
production environments running the old
生产环境运行旧
version right it's because we're going
版本正确是因为我们要
to be measuring these two things next to
测量旁边的两件事
each other and when we are measuring
彼此，当我们测量
metrics like system metrics then they
像系统指标之类的指标
could really be impacted by a start
可能真的会受到一个开始的影响
right or even if you're having your
正确的，即使您拥有自己的
instances running for a long time there
实例在那里长时间运行
might be memory leaks or something right
可能是内存泄漏或正确的东西
so if you're gonna be looking at memory
所以如果你要看记忆
consumption then that might just give
消费，那么可能会给
you a completely different view so just
您的看法完全不同，所以
having two new instances start up
启动两个新实例
actually we're spinning up four
其实我们正在旋转四个
instances in total two baselines and two
实例总共有两个基准和两个
Canaries so we can actually have some
金丝雀，所以我们实际上可以有一些
load there and that gives you this this
加载在那里，这给你这个
shared I mean this is this common
分享我的意思是这很普遍
baseline that you can work from so the
您可以使用的基准
the baseline will just flown it's from
基线只是飞来的
production right that's basically the
生产权基本上就是
current version production work loading
当前版本的生产工作负载
it and then the canary version that's
然后是金丝雀版本
actually coming from that's actually a
实际上来自那个
Highlander again coming from the same
汉兰达再次来自同一个
source as def so that's definitely the
来源为def，因此绝对是
latest version right so that's that's
正确的最新版本，那就是
basically what we want to start with so
基本上我们想从这里开始
if we look at the pipeline it's doing it
如果我们看着管道，它正在做
right this is pulling it if you look at
对，如果你看这就是拉
the infrastructure if you just look at
基础设施，如果您只看
production only and don't we refresh all
仅生产，不刷新所有
of a sudden we've got baseline and
突然之间我们有了基线
canary spinning up right so this is
金丝雀向上旋转，所以这是
these are two extra instances that are
这是两个额外的实例
going to be spun up next to the existing
将在现有的旁边旋转
cluster and I don't have any
集群，我没有任何集群
sophisticated low bouncing currently set
当前设置的复杂低反弹
up it just means that if I look at load
只是意味着如果我看着负载
balancers right and I refresh and at
平衡器正确，我刷新并在
some point it's going to show here that
某些点将在这里显示
my it's not just version two if I also
我不只是第二版
show instances my four instances of
显示实例我的四个实例
version two of production that that's
生产的第二个版本
going to receive traffic but also the
不仅要接收流量，
baseline and also the canary right so if
基线以及金丝雀的权利，如果
you all go to the same page right if you
你们所有人都去同一个页面
also start refreshing
也开始刷新
should be seeing the canary also being
应该看到金丝雀
fed to you of course this is not
喂给你当然不是
something as you can see here voila so
就像你在这里看到的那样
we have in total eight instances now I
现在我们总共有八个实例
just wanna make sure this works so I'm
只是想确保它可以工作，所以我
going to start doing some load some
将开始做一些负载
extra load that's because you know
额外的负载是因为你知道
sometimes I don't have enough load so
有时我没有足够的负担，所以
okay so I'm generating some load here
好吧，所以我在这里产生一些负载
just to make sure my music my my
只是为了确保我的音乐是我的
application has enough metrics to deal
应用程序具有足够的指标来处理
with and you can see here already that
与，你已经可以在这里看到
nice example rigs are being returned
返回了很好的示例装备
together right so if you start
一起吧，所以如果你开始
refreshing your page you will see that
刷新页面，您将看到
you'll have at some point you'll have
在某个时候你会拥有
music's and at some point you'll have
音乐，在某个时候你会
prickle break and that's actually the
抽搐休息，实际上是
that's actually is the canary playing
那实际上是金丝雀在玩
make I mean playing together with the
我的意思是和
current production version right refresh
当前生产版本右刷新
here some points there we go
这里有一些要点
you have the canary so we're now feeding
你有金丝雀，所以我们现在在喂
information into the canary and if I
信息进入金丝雀，如果我
look at my data dog it's now receiving
看我现在收到的数据狗
metrics from my baseline and from my
我的基准和我的指标
canary right and as you can see here I
金丝雀的权利，你可以在这里看到我
have two metrics that I care about
我关心两个指标
rendering time average and rendering
平均渲染时间和渲染
time maximum so I really want to care
时间最长，所以我真的很想关心
about how fast is it respond this to me
关于它对我的回复速度有多快
right because that's the chaos that we
对，因为那是我们的混乱
introduced and you can see here that the
介绍，您可以在这里看到
baseline has a bigger as it's actually
基线实际上更大
higher hmm that's a bit strange but it
较高的嗯，这有点奇怪，但是
starts still starting I hope this is
开始仍然开始我希望这是
going to you know fix itself
去你知道自己修复
we'll see that's why we do canary
我们会看到这就是为什么我们做金丝雀
testing right so if I look at my canary
测试正确，所以如果我看着我的金丝雀
here currently it's already running
目前它已经在运行
right oh let me go here sorry my canary
对，哦，让我去这里，对不起我的金丝雀
here is running and you can see that
这里正在运行，您可以看到
well it's actually not doing much right
好吧，实际上并没有做得很好
now why because my canary complex says
现在为什么因为我的金丝雀情结说
that my warmup period is 1 minutes we
我的热身期是1分钟
just want to get rid of these starts it
只是想摆脱这些开始
starts spikes you know a CPU and RAM you
开始峰值，您知道CPU和RAM
don't want to care about that my
不想在乎我
interval is 1 minutes and I already
间隔是1分钟，我已经
failed boundary which is really fast my
失败的边界，这真的很快
interval is 1 minute where it kind
间隔是1分钟
had one minute time to look at the
有一分钟的时间看
metrics and then it's going to do an
指标，然后它将
analysis right and then it's going to
分析正确，然后
step it's going to have a step of 10 so
一步要走10步
that means every 10 seconds you're gonna
这意味着您每10秒钟就要
have metrics and so what does it
有指标，这是什么
actually measure let's see so it's
实际测量，让我们看一下
looking at rendering time average CPU
看渲染时间平均CPU
let's first look at systemic so
让我们先来看一下系统性
systematic CPUs usage of the system and
系统的系统CPU使用率和
also the process JVM memory used and log
还要使用的进程JVM内存和日志
back events right so if there's any the
返回事件，所以如果有的话
original logs you know so all this
您知道的原始日志，所有这一切
information is gathered and then for
收集信息，然后
Rick and Morty on this side we look at
里克和莫蒂在这边我们来看
business metrics while these are not
商业指标，而这些不是
really business metrics but it could be
真正的业务指标，但这可能是
where you have rendering time average a
您的渲染时间平均为
rendering time maximum so let's take a
最长的渲染时间，让我们来
look here I hope that everything is
看这里，我希望一切都好
working fine should be fine
工作正常应该很好
so here you can see we didn't actually
所以在这里你可以看到我们实际上并没有
do the canary analysis and we looked at
做金丝雀分析，我们看着
the results that we got so let's take a
我们得到的结果，让我们来
look here
看这里
voila and here if I have to zoom out a
瞧，如果我要缩小
bit sorry for the people in the back so
为后面的人感到难过，所以
here you can see that memory consumption
在这里您可以看到内存消耗
is fine the deviation is like 1.4
很好，偏差像1.4
percent which is not much logback events
百分比不多的回滚事件
no errors in both cases CPU usage is
两种情况下都没有错误，CPU使用率是
about 11 percent but you know it gives
大约11％，但您知道
it more time it's still a pass and then
时间多了还是过一会儿
we see that the average rendering time
我们看到平均渲染时间
has increased with a hundred ninety
增加了一百九十
percent as you can see the blue line is
如您所见，蓝线是
canary it's a lot higher now right so
金丝雀现在高很多了，所以
the trends that we measured is that the
我们测量的趋势是
canary is dangerous and we should roll
金丝雀是危险的，我们应该滚动
back and then the rendering time maximum
返回，然后渲染时间最大
here as you can see it's low up higher
您可以在这里看到它的高低
and also thanks to you freshing of
也感谢您的新鲜
course and my random load and then we've
当然还有我的随机负荷，然后我们
got system CPU usage which is also still
获得了系统CPU使用率
fine
精细
so here you see that you know we have a
所以在这里您会看到您知道我们有一个
dangerous version because these metrics
危险版本，因为这些指标
don't actually show us a good story
并没有向我们展示一个好故事
right so we have to go back and think
对，所以我们必须回去思考
that actually is happening right now has
实际上现在正在发生的事情
happened I'm sorry
发生了我很抱歉
it's too fast is actually cleaning up
实在太快了
the canary so it's destroying the
金丝雀，所以它摧毁了
baseline and destroying the canary right
基线和破坏金丝雀的权利
which is priestly for so if you look at
这是牧师的，所以如果你看
the infrastructure it's all gone like
基础设施全部消失了
nothing happens and if you go to the
什么也没发生，如果你去
production version here they refresh
生产版本在这里刷新
it's back to the green version so this
回到绿色版本，所以这
is kind of how canary analysis can help
金丝雀分析如何提供帮助
in automatically figuring out by
在自动找出
your application is working not by doing
您的应用程序无法正常运行
and to end tests or a chain testing on
并结束测试或链式测试
an acceptance environment where
接受环境
everything is being held back and you
一切都被阻碍了，你
lose speed but actually going to
失去速度，但实际上会
production and testing in production
生产和生产中的测试
with real data and real users of course
当然还有真实数据和真实用户
while making sure that you have a blast
同时确保你有爆炸
radius as small as possible and that you
半径越小越好
can easily roll back if things do go
如果一切顺利，可以轻松回滚
wrong and so that's kind of the idea of
是错误的，这就是
automated canary analysis so if we go
自动金丝雀分析，如果我们去
back to the slides so speed and
回到幻灯片，所以速度和
confidence we've been talking about this
有信心我们一直在谈论这个
at the start right this is kind of what
在开始的时候，这就是
spinnaker is about it tries to get you
大三角帆是关于它试图让你
give you more speed in your delivery
使您的交货速度更快
while increasing your confidence right
同时增强信心
so that's that's kind of a unique
所以那是一种独特的
selling point I suppose if you want to
我想如果你想卖点
know more about the spinnaker
了解更多有关大三角帆的信息
specifically you have a free ebook
特别是您有一本免费的电子书
online if you just go to spinnaker dot
在线，如果你只是去大三角帆点
IO you can download this book it's about
IO，您可以下载这本关于
75 pages it's really simple I mean
75页，这真的很简单
really fast to read and it's it's going
读起来真的很快，而且很快
in much more detail about all these
关于所有这些的更多细节
things I talked about today and so it's
我今天谈论的事情，所以
definitely something I would advise to
我绝对会建议
read so I think that's it that's that's
阅读，所以我认为就是那样
the wrap I think if the slides will be
包裹，我想如果幻灯片将
on speaker deck if you just go to my
在扬声器甲板上，如果您只是去我的
name it's gonna be there on Twitter you
名称它将在Twitter上出现
can always send any messages or
可以随时发送任何消息或
questions you can reach this the
问题，你可以达到这个
spinnaker team themselves on slack right
大三角帆队自己在松弛的权利
so you can just go to spinnaker team
所以你可以去参加大三角帆队
that slack calm and people from Netflix
懈怠的平静和来自Netflix的人们
from Google from pivotal are all there
Google提供的所有关键功能
and helping people out on Stack Overflow
并帮助人们解决堆栈溢出问题
you can just ask questions on the
你可以问关于
spinnaker tag and of course all this
三角帆标签，当然还有所有这些
information is available on spinnaker IO
有关大三角帆IO的信息
as well so if there's any questions
同样，如果有任何问题
please ask but thanks already for your
请问，但已经感谢您
attention
注意
[Applause]
[掌声]
question
题
hi can you show a little bit how you
嗨，你能展示一点你如何
configure spinnaker to connect with data
配置大三角帆与数据连接
doc how it's my canary analysis how how
doc这是我的金丝雀分析如何
do you do it actual right so the canary
你真的做对吗，所以金丝雀
analysis right now so basically what I
现在进行分析，基本上我
have to do is I have my awesome spring
要做的是我的 Spring 很棒
good application it integrates with
与之集成的良好应用程序
micro micro meter or micro meter I don't
微米微米或微米我不
know which one and that would then
知道那一个然后那个
expose these metrics right however it
正确公开这些指标
kind of it doesn't know where to send
有点不知道该发送到哪里
them right for now so I have to have
现在就可以了，所以我必须
some environment variables that talent
一些有才能的环境变量
tell them to send it right so I think
告诉他们正确发送，所以我认为
I'm not mistaken here here I have
我在这里没有记错
metrics exported from micro meter right
从千分尺右侧导出的指标
to data talk specifically the data log
专门谈论数据日志
and my API key application key are
和我的API密钥应用程序密钥是
basically exposed on the dog itself so
基本上暴露在狗身上，所以
you can get it over there and then I put
你可以拿到那边，然后我放
them here in my deployment well let me
他们在我的部署中很好，让我
take this one here let's say my deploy
在这里拿这个说我的部署
canary right if I take a look at it
金丝雀的权利，如果我看一看
there are some environment variables and
有一些环境变量，
I hope you yeah okay I will change these
我希望你是的，我会改变这些
keys of course pretty visible anyway so
按键当然很明显，所以
here they are you know feel free to use
在这里，您知道可以随时使用
them but that's how I expose it right
他们，但这就是我正确地公开它的方式
and then it picks it up from the
然后从
environment it injects them and it just
环境注入他们，它只是
starts sending metrics which is pretty
开始发送非常漂亮的指标
straightforward right it also works a
直截了当的权利也可以
similar way for all the other ones that
其他所有方法都一样
micromotor supports any other questions
微型马达支持任何其他问题
all right
好吧
[Music]
[音乐]
you
您